

 \searrow

awdheshp145@gmail.com



6264276274



Gwalior, India



awdheshstudent.github.io/myportfolio/



linkedin.com/in/awdheshprasad-33b323173



github.com/awdhesh-student

SKILLS

Programming language: C, C++, HTML and CSS, javascript (reactjs), Nodejs, MySQl, Python











Communication and Presentation skills









MS Office









LANGUAGES

English

Full Professional Proficiency

Hind

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

INTERESTS

Had a interest on outdoor sports

Travelling with Collegues

Spending time with pet

Awdhesh Prasad

Had a well experienced and knowledge about solving the real life problems and very enthusiastic to learn and explore new things which would encourage me to bring my best and can be helpful for me as well as for an organization to whom I would work.

EDUCATION

MCA (Masters in Computer Application)

Madhav Institute of Technology and Science, Gwalior

09/2021 - 05/2023 78%

BCA (Bachelors in Computer Application)

Prestige Institute of Management and Research, Gwalior

08/2018 - 04/2021 74%

XII

Green Wood Public School

04/2017 - 06/2018 61%

Courses

Science(PCM)

X

Green Wood Public School

04/2015 - 05/2016 8.2 cgpa

EXPERIENCE

intership at Analysed, Varient labs (05/2022 - 08/2022)

Worked on the live project as **frontend developer** intern and tester in a team by which it helps our team for successfully created modules and user will had a great experience while working on it.

internship at The SmartBridge (05/2023 - Present)

Working as a full stack developer on the projects to develop dynamic websites using **MERN framework** and **RESTful apis**.

ACHEIVEMENTS

partcipated in trainning session of Dart and Flutter(level-1) held at ABVP-IIITM, Gwalior (2021)

partcipated in Coding Champ held at Prestige Institute of Management, Gwalior (2021)

NPTEL Certificate (07/2022 - 10/2022)

attended 3 months course on cloud computing organised by NPTEL(National Programme on Technology Enhanced Learning) and registered elite certificate.

ACADEMIC PROJECTS

Database Projects (CRUD Operations)

done project on Vaccine Management System using MS SQL and php language in which user can interact with the modules present in the project. User can register themselves using a register module for the vaccine drive and can do many more things in it. It is basically localhost server project worked on local terminal (personal computer)

Web Development

designed a user friendly static website on American Muscle Car using HTML and CSS. Github link: https://awdhesh-student.github.io/project-2/

Weather App

This is the Weather App designed by the help of HTML, CSS, JavaScript and Weather API by Rapid Api . It show all the information about the particular place like min and max temperatures, humidity info, etc entered by the user. Github link: https://awdhesh-student.github.jo/weather-app/